[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mammoths are members of the elephant family.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mercurys maximum elongation is 32.2 degrees.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the last name of the two brothers who have each won the Cy Young Award given to the best Major League Baseball pitchers?", "correct_answer": "Perry", "incorrect_answers": ["Niekro", "Dean", "Hernandez"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie Mean Girls hit American theatres?", "correct_answer": "2004", "incorrect_answers": ["2003", "2006", "2005"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "With what American city is the urban legend about the Sewer alligator mostly associated with?", "correct_answer": "New York City", "incorrect_answers": ["San Francisco", "Los Angeles", "Chicago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the age of 14, Angelina Jolie dropped out of her acting classes and started dreaming of this profession.", "correct_answer": "Mortician", "incorrect_answers": ["Singer", "Florist", "Kindergarten teacher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, how long is the sunspot cycle?", "correct_answer": "11.1 years", "incorrect_answers": ["10.4 years", "14.8 years", "14.8 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If it wasnt for the star getting her revenge at the end of this 2003 movie it would have been completely depressing.", "correct_answer": "Kill Bill Vol 1", "incorrect_answers": ["Kill Bill Vol 2", "Jumanji", "Charlies Angels"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the author of the novel The Silence of the Lambs which was adapted into a Big Five Academy Award-winning movie.", "correct_answer": "Thomas Harris", "incorrect_answers": ["Robin Moore", "Avery Corman", "James Ellroy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Disney/Pixar film The Incredibles, Buddys computer password is Cronos.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sumatran tiger is the smallest of all tigers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the distinctive feature of the sixth planet of the Solar System (counted from the Sun)?", "correct_answer": "Its equatorial rings", "incorrect_answers": ["Its gigantic craters", "Its active volcanoes", "Its silver coloring"]}]